Parviz Isaev

Dushanbe, Tajikistan +992(938)-83-38-38 parvizjan@inbox.ru

I'm a Data Analyst with more than 2 years of experience in telecommunication, banking and live streaming organizations. My favorite part of being an analyst is diving into data, performing research and creating value from it.



Education

· Dates (from-to)

 Name and type of organization providing education and training

 Principal subjects/occupational skills covered

· Level in national classification

· Dates (from-to)

• Name and type of organization providing education and training

 Principal subjects/occupational skills covered

· Level in national classification

· Dates (from-to)

• Name and type of organization providing education

 Principal subjects/occupational skills covered

· Level in national classification

2019 - 2022

China University of Mining and Technology

Internships

Data mining, Intermediate Econometrics, Introduction to Python

Master's degree in Management Science and Engineering

2015 - 2019

China University of Mining and Technology

Internships

Operations Management Research, Finance, Java EE, Web Front-End Frameworks, ERP, Logistics Management, Supply Chain Management Science, HTML5, Excel.

Bachelor's degree in E-business

2014 - 2015

Shanghai University

Chinese language

Chinese program diploma, Mandarin proficiency test level 4 (HSK 4)

Work experience

• Dates (from – to)

· Name and address of employer

• Type of business or sector

· Occupation or position held

• Main activities and responsibilities

29.04.2022-to present

"Mestum", Moscow city, Russian Federation.

Live Streaming Organization.

Data analyst.

Real-time dashboard: Backend (FastAPI), Frontend (HTML5, CSS3, JS) and Database (PostgreSQL).

Mestum Platform user analysis.

Dates (from – to)

· Name and address of employer

· Type of business or sector

· Occupation or position held

· Main activities and responsibilities

03.06.2021-25.04.2022

"Paymona", Dushanbe city, Tajikistan.

Outsourcing Startup. Provides such services as: Machine learning solutions and big data preprocessing and analysis.

Data analyst.

Implementation of various Machine learning models on Paymona startup website. The main goal is to introduce and illustrate the benefits of machine learning.

Churn prediction.

Credit scoring.

• Dates (from - to)

· Name and address of employer

• Type of business or sector

· Occupation or position held

· Main activities and responsibilities

10.12.2020-02.06.2021

CJSC «Indigo Tajikistan» (T-cell), Dushanbe city, Tajikistan.

Telecommunication company.

Intern in Management and Product department.

Customer Based Scan analysis.

NPS analysis. Churn prediction.

• Dates (from - to)

Name and address of employer

• Type of business or sector

· Occupation or position held

· Main activities and responsibilities

05.01.2019-20.03.2019

JSC "Alif Bank", Dushanbe city, Tajikistan.

Bank.

Intern in Technical department.

Installing POS terminal firmware.

Moderating Alif shop website.

Analyzing alipay and wechat pay.

• Dates (from – to)

· Name and address of employer

• Type of business or sector

· Occupation or position held

· Main activities and responsibilities

01.08.2018-01.09.2018

"Boommao" Marketing Services company, Moscow city, Russian Federation.

Marketing Services.

Assistant (intern) in E-Marketing department.

Define the marketing strategies for the company to help expand business and grow.

B2B business negotiations.

Moderating wechat mini programs.

• Dates (from - to)

· Name and address of employer

• Type of business or sector

· Occupation or position held

Main activities and responsibilities

Reading skills

Writina skills

Verbal skills

15.06.2016-30.08.2016

Huawei Technologies Co., Ltd in Tajikistan

Telecommunication company Intern in marketing department

Analyzing Tajikistan's market

Skills:

Languages: Mother tongue

Other languages

Tajik

English	Chinese	Russian	Uzbek	Turkish
Fluent	Fluent	Fluent	Basic Knowledge	Basic Knowledge
Fluent	Fluent	Good	Basic Knowledge	Basic Knowledge
Fluent	Fluent	Fluent	Basic Knowledge	Basic Knowledge

Social skills

Data collection, processing, and analysis, ambitious, full responsibility to the work performed, honest and, friendly, good communication skills, high sense of teamwork, a strong sense of purpose, the ability to remain calmness in stressful situations, make decisions and be responsible for their result

Technical skills

Python, Microsoft office, DEX language, Power BI, SPSS, HTML5, CSS3, Flask, Django, FastAPI, Javascript, MySQL, PostgreSQL.

Additional information

My achievements

- Certificate for the high-quality work conduction in Telecom company "Tcell"
- English proficiency test (IBT), score -75
- Mandarin proficiency test (HSK), HSK 6 (highest Chinese language proficiency exam in China)
- Certificates: Chinese, Turkish, Math, Chemistry, Boxing, Photography, Soccer, Basketball
- E-Business Innovation challenge. Got 3rd place in China University of Mining and Technology
- Chinese character competition. Got 2nd place in China University of Mining and Technology
- Chinese stage play competition. Got 1st place in Shanghai